[
  {
    "question": "apple",
    "answer": "Mela"
  },
  {
    "question": "traffic light",
    "answer": "Semaforo"
  },
  {
    "question": "strawberry",
    "answer": "Fragola"
  },
  {
    "question": "orange",
    "answer": "Arancia"
  },
  {
    "question": "horse",
    "answer": "Cavallo"
  },
  {
    "question": "handcuffs",
    "answer": "Manette"
  },
  {
    "question": "travel",
    "answer": "Viaggio"
  },
  {
    "question": "pistol (gun)",
    "answer": "Pistola"
  },
  {
    "question": "rocket (space travel)",
    "answer": "Razzo"
  },
  {
    "question": "calculator",
    "answer": "Calcolatrice"
  }
]